(Sheldon:)You want me to remove him from the team?
I'm the captain, I can do that.
(Penny:)No, no, that's okay. Just let me
talk to him and I'll get back to you.
(Sheldon:)-When are you going to talk to him?
-I don't know.
(Sheldon:)He's in the laundry room now.
Now would be a good time.
(Penny:)You're not gonna leave me
until I do it?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I think we both know
the answer to that question.
(Penny:)-I think we should talk now.
-What? No, it's okay.
We don't have to talk because
there's nothing to talk about.
(Leonard:)-Everything's good.
-Really?
So you didn't get snarky...
...because I said something nice
to a bowl of chili fries?
(Leonard:)All right, maybe I overreacted.
(Leonard:)So we're in two different places,
emotionally. So what?
(Leonard:)And maybe I'm a little ahead of you,
and that's fine.
(Leonard:)In fact, it makes sense,
because let's face it...
(Leonard:)...I've been in this relationship
two years longer than you.